mytechsupportstore.com 2011-06-02

# Privacy Policy - Mytechsupportstore.com

  * Home
  * Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets forth a full and complete statement of the privacy related practices and procedures adopted by Mytechsupportstore for its online technical support services. This Policy is effective as of the date set forth above, and will remain in effect and updated as this Policy provides.

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of the Terms and Conditions posted at <http://www.mytechsupportstore.com/terms-and-conditions.html>

Definitions:   
All information initially capitalized shall have the same meaning that is set forth in Terms and Conditions, of which the Privacy Policy is an integral part.

1) Customer's Information Collection and Use:  Mytechsupportstore is the sole owner of the information collected through the website/phone/e-mail. The company will not sell or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this policy.

a) Personal Information: Mytechsupportstore will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allow us to contact you. In order to use our services, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, the user is required to give the user contact information (such as First and Last name, E-mail address, Postal address, Personal identifier etc.). Mytechsupportstore will use your contact details to contact you regarding the product and/or services that you have requested for. This includes re-registration/renewal notifications, special offers, and surveys on improving our services.

b) Payment Information: If any user opts for the service provided by Mytechsuportstore then we will collect his or her credit card information, and other payment information necessary to complete a payment from user. Mytechsupportstore may use a third party to process and verify credit cards for billing purposes. This requires us to share user name, credit card number, expiration date and billing address with the credit card processing company. When processing a payment transaction, Mytechsupportstore will also obtain information regarding the amount of the payment and other transaction data. We may transfer or disclose this payment information to a third party only to the extent necessary in order to complete a customer's payment processing.

c) Computer System Information

i) Subscriber Computer: Mytechsupportstore may also ask for information related to your computer. The information may include the date of purchase of your computer, type of computer, identification number of your computer, software or peripherals attached to it, make and model of your computer and/or any computer hardware, attached to it, condition of the computer, system, registry data about software installations and hardware configurations, and error tracking files. Generally, this information is required to provide a personalized tech support to you, and this helps us update our online technical support tools and enhance our supported products list.

ii) Diagnostic Tool: Some of our online diagnostic application may collect a wide variety of useful information about the state of a computer system and the applications on it. This information is packaged into a document containing all the essential details needed by Mytechsupportstore and is sent securely over the Internet to the server or a third party server appointed by Mytechsupportstore. Then our expert analyzes this information to help to diagnose and solve end-user problems. Information collected by the Mytechsuportstore application will not contain any sensitive information such as the number of websites visited, e-mail messages, e-mail addresses sent to, passwords, profiles, etc. Use of the Remote Access and Diagnoses applications is also subject to the terms of use in the respective software license agreements.  
Use of the Remote Access and Diagnoses applications is also subject to the terms of use in the respective software license agreements.

iii) Remote Access: While requesting a remote PC support from us you may request for the problem to be resolved by taking control of your computer. Mytechsupportstore uses qualified tools which allow user to grant control of the user computer to our tech expert remotely over the Internet, so that our expert can diagnose or correct problems. Our technicians are not allowed to use the Remote Access software unless they have the specialized training and user's consent to do so. In addition, Experts will not use Remote Access tools to obtain confidential or sensitive information stored on user computer or network, deliberately destroy information on user computer or network, or cause user to experience system problems.

d) Live Help Session Records: Mytechsupportstore reserves the right to monitor on-line and off-line sessions between the user and our technical expert for quality control of the services provided by us to our Customer by our Technical Support Executive. In addition, we may also record on-line and off-line sessions conducted on the website for user reference and to assist in resolution of disputes and/or potential complaints. The session records will help us to improve our services, build a support knowledge base, and/or conduct internal market research. The session record data will not be correlated with personally identifiable data about any individual customers.

e) Cookies: A cookie is a message given to a Web browser by a Web server. It is a browser feature and assigns a unique identification to your computer. The cookie also makes our website more responsive to our customer's need. The browser stores the message in a text file. The main purpose of cookies is to identify users and possibly prepare customized Web pages for them. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site and cannot infringe the privacy of our customers.

f) Log Files: Mytechsupportstore uses some unique IP addresses to analyze market trends, administer our website, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

g) Sharing: Mytechsupportstore will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is usually not related to any personal information that can identify any individual person, unless specifically required to do so.

h) Children's Online Policy: No part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13. Consistent with the Children's Online privacy Protection Act, we do not collect or maintain information at our website or sell products to those we actually know are under the age of 13. Please ask your parent or guardian to assist you in using our services if you are under the age of 13.

i) Surveys & Contests: From time-to-time Mytechsupportstore sends requests information from user via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to participate. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our services.

2) Security: Mytechsupportstore takes every precaution to protect information of customers. When the user submits sensitive information via the website, the user information is protected both on-line and off-line. When our registration form asks user to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), the information is encrypted and is protected with the best of the encryption software. While on a secure page, such as our registration form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when user is just 'surfing'.

We use encryption to protect sensitive information online; we also do everything which is in our hands to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information which is mentioned above, is restricted to our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our customer service representative or billing clerk) are granted access to personal information. Our employees use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to regain access to user information.

Furthermore, ALL employees are kept updated about our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. In situations that are required by law, we may disclose some information about our users to law-enforcing officers.

3)Supplementation Of Information: In order to properly fulfill obligation towards our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from Third party sources. For example, to determine the creditworthiness of our customer, we may use their name or other related information to request a credit report. Once we determine the creditworthiness of our customers, this document is destroyed.

a) Notification of Changes: Mytechsupportstore reserves the right to update this privacy Policy from time to time by posting changes online without notifying you. The most current version of the privacy Policy can be reviewed by clicking on the "privacy Policy" hypertext link located on our website http://www.mytechsupportstore.com/. It is your responsibility to refer to this privacy Policy before submitting any information on the website. Submitting your information after such changes to the privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those posted changes.

b)Correction/Updating Personal Information: If the customer personally identifiable information changes (such as user zip code), or the customer no longer desire the Service, then we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove personal data of the customer provided to us.

c) Changes to This Privacy Policy: If at any point Mytechsupportstore decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify our customers via e-mail. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If you have any queries about our privacy policy, feel free to mail us at [contact@mytechsupportstore.com](mailto:contact@mytechsupportstore.com)
